devsteam.com 2017-06-25

# Privacy Policy - DevsTeam

Your Privacy is extremely important to us. At DevsTeam we have some fundamental policies that we strictly maintain.

– We never share your personal Email Address with anybody else that you used to perform various service or information queries.

– We sometimes need your IP Address, Location, Search Terms and we store it for the internal site structuring improvement only. We never share or disclose this anywhere. 

– We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.

– We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.

– We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

– In our blogging products, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

– Cookies and Web Beacons: We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

– Our Brand name “DevsTeam” is trademarked and all the related domains and names are the sole property of DevsTeam Limited. Any illegal usages of our Brand name is against of our privacy policy & TOS and we have right to send legal notice if anyone misusages our brand name.

– Our Services are always properly implemented and proved that these are working. If some disasters found in any services, we will recheck it and send another plans to fix it. But, we are not committed to take the responsibilities as problems always exist in client’s end.

– Comments and other content submitted to our Akismet anti-spam service are not saved on our servers unless they were marked as false positives, in which case we store them long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future false positives.

– We also use third party advertisements on http://devsteam.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

– DoubleClick DART cookies: We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting doubleclick.com 

– You hereby declare that; You ( a client or Visitor) are thoroughly abide by all the rules & regulations (laws of the company) of DevsTeam with due respect to the Terms & Conditions (user policy) and learning policies. You are well-aware of that DevsTeam authority (directors or departmental chief) can change the Service Cost anytime they want according to the continuous updates of Tech world and the giants of respective company terms or algorithms. The brochures, Audios, Videos and all other learning materials provided by DevsTeam are copyrighted with all rights reserved and you will not publish it to anywhere out of DevsTeam without having any written or verbal acquiescence. You will never disrespect DevsTeam (property & brands) or its Team (directors & employees) to any public places at any cost.

– If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our support team.
